# Mihai Tuhari



mihai.tuhari@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/mihaituhari



+40740145184



https://github.com/mihaituhari/

## Summary

Geek since early ages, growing up with C++, I joined the #webdev industry and started coding back in 2003. Since then I am constantly experiencing & tackling new challenges, as well as new technologies.

Specialties: PHP, MySQL, Laravel, Redis, RabbitMQ, Elasticsearch, CSS, JavaScript, Vue, API integration & much more.

More about me @ https://github.com/mihaituhari https://mihai.tuhari.ro

## **Experience**



### 👋 Software Engineering Manager

Everli

Jan 2022 - Present (1 year 1 month)

- \*Summary:\*
- Engineering Manager of "Lower Funnel" squad, which consists of mixed platform developers (backend, frontend, iOS, Android)
- Responsible of the entire in-store experience, up to the checkout and order lifecycle.
- At heart, a fullstack developer (backend mostly) actively working with PHP, Laravel, MySQL, RabbitMQ, Redis, Elasticsearch and more.
- \*Daily responsibilities:\*
- Lead & inspire the developers team, in an Agile way
- Communicate & plan efficiently with Product team, as well as UI/UX team
- Scoping and planning activities which are cross-component
- Responsible of the Sprint Planning
- Own the Agile ceremonies (daily stand-up, Sprint Plan, Sprint Retrospective)
- Code review across multiple teams
- Supervise CI/CD release processes
- \*Mission:\*
- Optimize customer In-Store experience and increase "Store to Checkout conversion rate" by improving the way customers can find, discover and order/reorder the products they want.
- Maximize brand revenues for the company while providing relevant content to the consumers and increasing ROI for the brand.
- Improve the Checkout flow by providing flexibility to the customer, along with option of choosing replacements for products which might be out of stock.
- \*Soft-skill responsibilities:\*
- Being involved in the recruitment process, for multiple teams
- Helping team grow, through assignment and evaluation of goals, as well as internal level & salary

- Define guidelines for Jira/Confluence templates & ways of working



### 🚾 Founder, President, Web Developer, Project Manager

Rescue 4x4

Nov 2015 - Present (7 years 3 months)

Combining my passions for off-road and web development I created an unique platform which puts in contact the offroad enthusiasts with the people in trouble. When an incident is reported, the system automatically notifies via SMS and email the members who are covering the area of the person who needs help. The system also pushes the incident to Waze as an accident pinpoint with summary of the incident.

The project is already showing it's benefits, the community having solved all the reported incidents. Rescue 4x4 community already covers more than 1000 active members who have joined the platform as volunteers, willing to help. Recently it also turned into a non governmental organization, looking to assist and train the members.

Also the NGO of Rescue4x4 has signed agreements with local authorities responsible for emergency situations as well as ambulance service in order to assist the organizations.

https://www.rescue4x4.ro/



### \max Tech Lead

#### Everli

Oct 2019 - May 2022 (2 years 8 months)

Full stack developer and tech lead of mixed platform developers team.

#### Mission:

- Optimize customer In-Store experience and increase "Store to Checkout conversion rate" by improving the way customers can find, discover and order/reorder the products they want.
- Maximize brand revenues for the company while providing relevant content to the consumers and increasing ROI for the brand.

#### KPIs:

- Store conversion rate
- Search conversion rate
- AOV (Average order value)
- Brand revenues



### Full-stack Web Developer

#### Everli

Jun 2017 - Oct 2019 (2 years 5 months)

Working together with the colleagues from Verona & Milano, improving and enhancing supermercato24.it platform and components.

Responsible of developing new important features as well as the search engine, based on Elasticsearch, Laravel, Angular and RabbitMQ.

### Senior Web Developer

Soft Galaxy

Jan 2016 - Sep 2017 (1 year 9 months)

Being part of a young and dedicated team, I learned a lot and I also passed my knowledge to the other team members.

I was responsible for developing the main CMS which is used for all the projects of the company. The base technologies behind our proprietary CMS are: Laravel, PHP7, MySQL, HTML, CSS, JavaScript and jQuery. Based on the project and client requirements we could easily integrate other technologies such as RabbitMQ, WebSockets, eBay API etc.

Once the CMS was developed I held workshops and tutorials with the other developers from the company.

The projects I developed (from scratch) cover a wide range, from e-commerce platforms to custom API developed for iOS/Android applications.

I also managed a team of front-end developers and designers, with which I had a great professional relationship and we delivered together the projects in time and at best quality.

## Senior Web Developer

Aug 2008 - Jan 2016 (7 years 6 months)

While working at WebManage I implemented websites and custom web based solutions for clients across Australia and world-wide. Being located in Bucharest and being a full-time remote work for Sydney, the entire communication was done via Skype, emails and our internal ticketing system.

## IT Manager & Software Developer

Mirusan Prod

Jun 2005 - Jun 2008 (3 years 1 month)

## Web Developer

Webxis

Jul 2007 - Jan 2008 (7 months)

### **Education**



### University POLITEHNICA of Bucharest

2005 - 2008

## Colegiul National 'Mihai Viteazul' Bucharest

Mathematics, Physics, Informatics 2001 - 2005

## 🕠 Universitatea Bucuresti, Facultatea de Matematica-Informatica

Mathematics, IT

2010 - Present

## Skills

PHP • MySQL • Elasticsearch • Redis • RabbitMQ • Team Leadership • Full-Stack Development • Back-End Web Development • Team Leadership • JavaScript